The ending of "Hajime Shacho".
The idol's costume is so lame.
Nighttime.
Nighttime and idols.
So, let's get to it. I'll get right to it.
I would like to go to the top corner of this nighttime section's specialty.
Yes, I'll go to the main project.
Let's go to the main project.
Please give the title call to ℃-ute.
Yes. My three generations of four heads.
This is a special corner where we ask you to introduce the three elements that make up who you are.
Now then, Mr. Kojima, I would like to ask you to tell us about your three elements.
Here are my three major elements!
One Piece Continuity, and Gap Moe!
Okay, let's get started.
I'm going to ask you one by one.
One Piece. As you can see, I love One Piece.
By the way, I went to buy the latest issue of One Piece as soon as it went on sale today. I knew that One Piece was the first thing that made up who I am.
The reason why I fell in love with One Piece is because I recently started reading it. I was in the first grade of junior high school.
I started reading One Piece by chance because I thought it was famous, and I was really into it, but it was One Piece after all.
I was almost made because of One Piece. 90% of my life is really like One Piece. My dream for the future is to sing the theme song of One Piece.
I really don't want to give this up to anyone, and I don't think anyone else has sung it among the Stapler idols.
I don't think anyone else has sung this song among the staple idols, so I am doing my best with the feeling that I will not give up.
When you read One Piece in junior high school, how did you get hooked on it? That's right. I used to read a lot of manga, but I never got into boys' manga.
I was reading a lot of shoujo manga, but I happened to run out of things to look at at the bookstore, and I was wondering what I should read.
I was wondering what I should read, and I happened to pick it up and I was hooked from then on.
By the way, what is your favorite episode? I really love all of them, but the one I like the most is the one with the two top characters.
The first one is in the Baratie Arc, where Luffy is wearing Don Creek's sword, that sword mountain cape called "Yama Manto.
There is a scene in the Baratie episode where Luffy protects Don Creek's cloak that is covered with swords and beats Don Creek.
Anyone know what I'm talking about? I think everyone understands it because everyone on the staff is nodding their heads. I'm sure everyone understands. I love it so much.
That scene is the most surprising scene in One Piece since it started in the first volume, which is about volume 8.That was the scene that surprised me the most in One Piece since it started in the first volume, which was about volume 8.
I would never have hit him with a sword, so I really liked that scene because it showed how cool the main character was.
Another scene that I really liked was the scene in Punk Hazard when they were on their way to the dress loader, and they were talking about the g5 and the navy and the Straw Hat gang.
The Navy and the Straw Hat gang are enemies because they are pirates and the Navy.
They had been fighting together up to that point.
But when they parted, the Navy said that pirates are no good... that it's impossible.
And the Straw Hat crew was like, "What's the matter with him?
Then there was a scene where she said that the Navy would fall in love with the Straw Hat crew if they didn't speak ill of them.
I love that part where the navy falls in love with the pirates.
It's like everyone else is trying to say the same thing.
Do you know what I mean?
I feel like I could talk about One Piece for about 30 minutes, but you want me to go on.
Yes, but I don't have enough time to finish.
Yes, I have to finish.
The quality of your work was so good that it was even featured in an article, wasn't it?
Yes, and you were featured in the article.
I'm sorry, I don't want to do that to you, Mr. Natali.
This program is...
Celery, who loves Hana-chan
Nai-chan
Mameyome
Tachi-san
Pudding-san provided the entertainment!
I love you all!
Keep up the good work!